

Darya Kuliashova

Frontend Developer

I'm a Frontend Developer boasting more than 3 years in the field. I personify self-discipline, dedication to results, continuous learning, skill refinement, unwavering persistence, and determination to reach objectives. I embrace responsibilities confidently, welcome constructive criticism, and bring a good sense of humor.

I am skilled in HTML5 (semantics), CSS3/SCSS, JavaScript, and Cross-Browser Compatibility, as well as in React.js, RestAPIs, and Git. I have successfully implemented team and individual projects using the above technologies, including Node.js, and NestJS.

CONTACTS

+48 698 149 204

🔀 daria.kuliashova@gmail.com

in <u>LinkedIn</u>

GitHub

Białystok, Poland

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML5 / CSS / SASS / JS ES6+
- REACT.JS / REACT ROUTER
- REACT HOOKS
- REACT BOOTSTRAP
- REDUX / REDUX PERSIST
- RTK QUERY / REDUX THUNK
- GIT / GITHUB / GITLAB
- WEBPACK / DOCKER
- REST API / AXIOS
- NPM / YARN
- NODE.JS / EXPRESS / NEST.JS
- MONGODB / MONGOOSE / MYSQL

SOFT SKILLS

- RESPONSIBILITY
- TEAMWORK
- RESULT-ORIENTED
- SOCIABLE
- FAST LEARNER
- OPTIMISTIC

LANGUAGES

- ENGLISH INTERMEDIATE
- POLISH UPPER-INTERMEDIATE
- RUSSIAN NATIVE

EDUCATION

FULL STACK DEVELOPER | IT SCHOOL GOIT

OCTOBER 2020 - OCTOBER 2021

MARKETER-ECONOMIST |
POLESSKY STATE UNIVERSITY

SEPTEMBER 2014 - MARCH 2017

COMMERCIAL ACTIVITY |
COLLEGE OF ECONOMICS AND
MANAGEMENT

SEPTEMBER 2007 - JULY 2009

PROJECTS

1. SCOOTAPI

a platform for managing an e-scooter fleet https://scootapi.com/en

[React, React Hooks, Redux, Ant design, TypeScript, Docker, RESTFUL API]

2. HOLIDAYS

management system for scheduling vacations and absence of employees

https://github.com/darya425/super_holidays/tree/dev https://github.com/darya425/super_holidays_backend/tree/dev

[React, Ant design, Axios, NestJS, MySQL]

3. EVENT-BOOSTER

project to search for current events

https://github.com/darya425/event-booster

[HTML5, SASS, Handlebars Template, RESTFUL API, vanilla JS, Responsive design]

4. BESTHOMETENERIFE

real estate search project

https://besthometenerife.com/

[Wordpress]

5. ASTANBUD

company information page https://astanbud.pl/

[Wordpress]

WORK EXPERIENCE

SCOOTAPI

PART-TIME | ADMIN PANEL DEVELOPMENT

NOVEMBER 2021 - CURRENTLY

- Creating new application modules using React,
- Working with existing code, incl. optimization tasks,
- Code refactoring,
- Designing the architecture of the application (SPA),
- Settings up and using Docker,
- Code-reviews,

BEST INVEST | PART-TIME | PROJECT DEVELOPMENT

2019 - CURRENTLY

- Development and support of the project

ACCOUNTANT

SEPTEMBER 2009 - SEPTEMBER 2021 | BELARUS | POLAND